(Leonard:)Forget the robot. What happened to you?
- He slipped and fell.
- Yes.
(Howard:)I slipped and fell.
(Howard:)In the bathroom.
(Howard:)Bounced right off the tub.
(Penny:)Yes. Now he knows
what bathtubs are capable of doing...
(Penny:)...when you don't treat them
with respect.
(Sheldon:)Yeah.
They sucker-punch you
when your eyes are closed.
(Sheldon:)So, what do you think, Howard?
It... It's not that bad, right?
Yeah, no.
A little electrical tape, some solder...
(Howard:)Are you insane?
(Howard:)I've seen space probes that crashed into the
desert that were in better shape than this.
(Sheldon:)You're right.
(Sheldon:)Monte's gone.
(Sheldon:)We'll bury him in the morning.
A simple ceremony. I'll speak.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, you'll play your cello.
(Penny:)Sheldon, honey, aren't you getting a little
carried away? I mean, it's just a toy robot.
(Sheldon:)Just a toy robot?
(Penny:)Penny.
(Penny:)I know, I got it.
Sheldon? I'm sorry.
(Howard:)Well, don't get the wrong idea.
(Howard:)The way I see it,
I'm halfway to pity sex.